<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conversational Commerce on FARFETCH Chat | MultiModal Conversational Agents</title>
    <link>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/tags/conversational-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conversational Commerce on FARFETCH Chat | MultiModal Conversational Agents</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2019 [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 11:59:01 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://farfetch-chat.github.io/tags/conversational-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>iFetch @ 2022 CMU Portugal Summit - A review</title>
      <link>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20221121/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 11:59:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20221121/</guid>
      <description>We were delighted to be invited by CMU Portugal to participate in the Program&amp;rsquo;s conference meeting on November 9-10th at the Hub Criativo do Beato, Lisboa. The conference was followed by a meeting of the Program Board and External Review Committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iFetch @ 2022 CMU Portugal Summit and an introduction to iFetch</title>
      <link>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20221107/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 21:00:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20221107/</guid>
      <description>Our teams will be present at the upcoming Carnegie Mellon Portugal Program (CMU) Summit 2022 - New Frontiers in Tech to speak more about the iFetch project. The CMU Portugal Summit 2022 brings together experts from Portuguese universities, Carnegie Mellon University, and companies to present ICT research progress in areas as diverse as Health, Forests, Security, Artificial Intelligence, Language Technologies, Machine learning, among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Understanding for Conversational AI </title>
      <link>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20220719/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 10:00:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20220719/</guid>
      <description>Summary Natural Language Understanding (NLU) is an important field of Natural Language Processing, which enables several applications ranging from question answering to fully automated conversational agents. In practice, the NLU is the first step of a conversational agent that processes the user’s raw utterance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why are time-series databases relevant for a Conversational AI platform? </title>
      <link>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20220422/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 16:45:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20220422/</guid>
      <description>What is time-series data? Time-series data is present everywhere, and typically, we are talking about significant amounts of data. Time-series data typically consists of data points that may represent instances of events that are tracked and aggregated continuously over a period of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FARFETCH is a Sponsor of VISUM 2021 Summer School</title>
      <link>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20210401/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 10:45:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20210401/</guid>
      <description>FARFETCH is sponsoring VISUM summer school. iFetch team is happy to take part in this initiate by proposing a new project under the umbrella of information retrieval (with application on conversational agents) that VISUM applicants will need to address throughout the summer school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Publication at ACM MM 2020</title>
      <link>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20201022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 10:45:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20201022/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to announce that our recent publication is now available at ACM digital library.
Title: Adaptive temporal triplet-loss for cross-modal embedding learning.
Abstract: &amp;ldquo;There are many domains where the temporal dimension is critical to unveil how different modalities, such as images and texts, are correlated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Conversational AI - ACM Multimedia 2020 workshop</title>
      <link>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20201002/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 11:23:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farfetch-chat.github.io/blog/blog-post-20201002/</guid>
      <description>We are organizing a workshop at ACM Multimedia 2020 - Multimodal Conversational AI (MuCAI).
Conversational agents are now becoming a commodity as a number of companies push for this technology. The wide use of these conversational agents exposes the many challenges in achieving more natural, human-like, and engaging conversational agents.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
